{
    "subject": "Carol_I_of_Romania",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Elisabeth_of_Wied",
    "human_readable": "Carol I of Romania is married to Elisabeth of Wied.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9880961179733276,
            "question": "Is there a marriage connection between Carol I of Romania and Elisabeth of Wied?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.963270366191864,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Carol I of Romania and Elisabeth of Wied?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9363395571708679,
            "question": "Was Carol I of Romania married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9359041452407837,
            "question": "Name the person married to Elisabeth of Wied."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9348762631416321,
            "question": "Who is Carol I of Romania married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9096226096153259,
            "question": "To whom was Elisabeth of Wied married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9044920206069946,
            "question": "Who is Elisabeth of Wied married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8965269327163696,
            "question": "Who was the wife of Carol I of Romania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8214330077171326,
            "question": "Identify the spouse of Carol I of Romania."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6344296932220459,
            "question": "What was the name of Elisabeth's spouse?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Carol I of Romania is married to Elisabeth of Wied.",
            "html": "yago_28971_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Identify the spouse of Carol I of Romania.",
            "html": "yago_28971_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the wife of Carol I of Romania?",
            "html": "yago_28971_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Elisabeth of Wied married to?",
            "html": "yago_28971_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28971_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28971_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28971_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28971_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28971_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28971_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28971_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28971_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28971_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28971_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Elisabeth of Wied was the Queen of Romania as the wife of King Carol I, which supports the triple that Carol I of Romania is married to Elisabeth of Wied."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Elisabeth of Wied was indeed the wife of King Carol I of Romania, supporting the statement that Carol I of Romania is married to Elisabeth of Wied."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}